

# TROY THEERANUNTAWAT

## VISUAL DESIGNER

Creative and detail-driven designer with a decade of experience in visual design and technical expertise from 10+ years at Apple. Seeking to advance into a Career Experience focused on graphic and UX/UI design, delivering impactful, user-centered solutions.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## Apple Inc.



- · As a visual designer for the Retail Learning & Development Team, I illustrated graphics for training material within Apple's Global Retail Sector.
- Partnered with various project managers over the globe, the Visual Designer in conjunction with the media team was able to facilitate graphics for Instructional Designers on a vast array of subjects from products to internal processes. Also maintained all digital assets within Apple retail's eDAM system.

February 2021 - June 2021 | Cupertino, California, United States

# Apple Inc. - Retail

Technical Specialist & Apple at Home Support Chat Specialist

- Diagnosed and repaired a wide array of Apple products including iPhones, iPads, Apple Watches, Apple TV, & Apple Vision Pro, ensuring excellent service and reliability.
- Provided strong technical support for both iOS software and hardware issues, ensuring consistent customer focus while maintaining a high customer satisfaction score of at least 80% and above (NPS).
- Exhibited strong multitasking and time management skills, efficiently handling an average of 3.3 sessions per queued hour while working with multiple customers simultaneously.
- · Provided mentorship and training to onboarding new Technical Specialists by supplying the tools necessary for problem solving & technical expertise.
- Consistent drive for results by providing solutions to customers as related to Apple Intelligence, Apple Care, Business Solutions, & Future Ownership.
- Effectively handled customer conflicts autonomously, requiring minimal management support.

November 2006 - Present | Pasadena, California, United States / Austin, Texas, United States

### Brandswalk BRANDSWALK

### **Graphic Designer**

- Freelance graphic designer for Brandswalk, a retail store based out of Orange County. Developed all print material for the store including signage, email blasts, and smaller web assets such as online banners and social networking material.
- Developed signage campaigns for multiple electronics brands such as Mophie, Incase, and CES.

November 2015 - December 2016 | Los Angeles, California, United States

### The Reef ATHE REEF

#### Art Director

• LA Mart, which served the greater downtown Los Angeles area for the latter part of the last 50 years as a hub for showcases and trade shows for goods and services has gone through a major rebranding to come into a more modern look. As part of their creative team, I helped transition their branding from being the LA Mart to what's now known as The Reef. Under new art direction, I facilitated all their new digital assets from web design, print, and building signage.

## WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

# Morningstar Entertainment morningstar

#### **Motion Graphic Artist**

- · Assisted principal Visual Effects Coordinator and Producer in developing graphics for "Triggers: Weapons that Changed the World" for the Discovery Channel.
- Graphics included rendering artwork in Photoshop, rotoscope, and digital camera orientation for certain graphics within the series.

October 2011 - December 2011 | Burbank, California, United States

## The Refinery Creative

#### Art Director Intern

- Under the direction of the Principal Creative Director and Account Representatives, I assisted with concept and execution with a variety of Key Art for all clients.
   Clients include: Warner Home Entertainment, Vivendi Entertainment, WWE, FX, and Home Media Magazine.
- Key Art Development included DVD Amarays, Blu-Ray Amarays, Disc Art, Commercial Magazine Trade Ads, Billing Block Development, Mechanicals, and occasional One Sheet work. All Art Development was in house under the Home Entertainment Division.

May 2011 - July 2011 | Sherman Oaks, California, United States

#### **EDUCATION**

CareerFoundry
Bootcamp Certificate in User Interface Design
December 2023 - Present | Berlin, Germany

California State University, Long Beach BA in Art with an emphasis in Graphic Design/Minor in Marketing

August 2003 - December 2006 | Long Beach, California, United States

#### **SKILLS**

Adobe Creative Suite, Illustration, Design & Layout, MacOS, iOS, HTML & CSS, Digital Asset Management, Slack, WebEX, Workfront, Keynote, Pages, Microsoft Office Suite, Zoom, Strong Communication Skills, Figma, Facilitation to Collaborate.







